<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Goodnights Comedy Club Events</title>
    <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events</link>
    <description>Comedy events at Goodnights Comedy Club in Raleigh, NC</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:15:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Chris Andrade (EN ESPAÑOL) (THIS SHOW IS COMPLETELY IN SPANISH WITH NO TRANSLATION) (April 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129129</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129129</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Chris Andrade, del primer podcast del mundo Escuela de Nada, nos presenta Chris Andrade en vivo: Una noche de comedia repleta de risas, alegrías y diversión. Y también sexo.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/78761/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Josh Mandl (April 23 - April 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129126</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129126</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Josh Mandl is a 23-year-old comedian. At 19 years-old, he started stand-up in Boston and now splits his time between New York City and touring. In 2021, he founded Next Stop Comedy, a stand-up organization that brings comedians to 100+ venues all over the country. More recently, his videos have amassed over 1.5 million views on Instagram, in just a couple of weeks. When he’s not on stage, he’s probably filming another sketch in his apartment and wondering if it’s too weird to post.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85299/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ms. Renee (April 26)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129122</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129122</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>HollywoodGenGen, widely recognized as "Miss Renee", is an acclaimed actor, comedian, and social media influencer celebrated for their ability to connect with audiences through humor and storytelling. With an impressive following that includes over 3.5 million TikTok followers, 600,000 Facebook followers, 200,000 YouTube subscribers, and 600,000 Instagram followers, Miss Renee has built a dynamic online presence characterized by entertaining and relatable comedy sketches. Their content resonates with millions, showcasing everyday life, work experiences, and unforgettable characters that keep fans coming back for more. Miss Renee's comedy stands out for its vivid, relatable storytelling, drawing inspiration from roles as a teacher, funeral home worker, and other unique jobs that provide endless material for laughs. On stage, HollywoodGenGen’s comedic talents shine even brighter. They have had the privilege of opening for the renowned actress and comedian Cocoa Brown, bringing laughter to audiences across the country. Their stand-up performances have graced iconic venues such as the Funny Bone Comedy Club and well-known clubs in the US. A true entertainer, HollywoodGenGen</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/73858/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapel Lacey (April 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129121</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129121</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Shapel Lacey is a Los Angeles based comedian born and raised in Mesa, Arizona. A diehard punk rocker and former award-winning competitive cheerleader, Shapel found ways to express himself and own his individuality at an early age. Shapel was cheerleading competitively for University of Louisville when someone dared him to take the stage as a comedian and he never looked back, dropping out shortly thereafter to pursue a career in stand up full-time. His unique life experiences such as having 3 dads, his punk rock mentality, and his stage presence make for a truly original voice in the comedy community. Diligence and the desire to grow led Shapel from the Phoenix open mic circuit onto main stages in Los Angeles, where he regularly performs at The Comedy Store, Laugh Factory and Hollywood Improv. Shapel has a 30 minute special out through Don’t Tell Comedy, called “Three Dads, Two Moms.” and can be seen headlining comedy clubs across the country.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/55648/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Allen: My First Final Farewell Tour (March 21)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129119</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129119</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Jeff Allen may (or may not) want to admit it, but he’s getting old. At 69, Jeff is staring down his 70th year and decided it might be time to think about slowing down. The result? My First Final Farewell Tour kicks off March 1st, 2026. Yes, you read that right—“First” and “Final” in the same sentence—because Jeff’s not totally sure he’s done. (After all, Cher had 20 farewell tours, and Elton John is still out there.) What he is sure of: he’s bringing a mix of fan favorites and fresh new material to the stage. From the classic Happy Wife Happy Life routine you’ve been quoting for years, to fresh takes on marriage, family, and everyday life, Jeff is pulling it all together for a night that’s hilarious, unforgettable, and uplifting. Jeff Allen is one of America’s most beloved comedians, with nearly 1 billion online views and a record-setting seven Dry Bar Comedy specials. He’s been featured on America’s Got Talent, The Today Show, Comedy Central, Showtime, and starred in the films Apostles of Comedy and My 7 Grandmas. Millions have seen him across Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, and YouTube—but nothing compares to seeing Jeff live.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/86530/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaron Myers (February 28)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129118</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129118</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Jaron Myers is a stand-up comedian from Missouri whose viral videos have racked up over 1 billion views across social media. With a dedicated following of more than a million fans, Jaron is known for his joyful energy, sharp storytelling, and clean comedy that connects with audiences of all ages. His breakout special The Blind Date — where Jaron went on a real first date in front of a live audience — captivated millions online and ended in a surprising twist: he married her. Jaron has two stand-up specials on Amazon Prime, a DryBar Comedy special, and co-hosts the hit educational comedy podcast Things I Learned Last Night. He tours nationally, delivering live shows that are hilarious, heartwarming, and rooted in a message of hope.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/86416/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodnights Comedy Academy: Comedy Workshop (January 17)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128352</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128352</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Get a one-day all intensive taste of our week-long comedy academy in one day!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/71687/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Brendan Sagalow (May 07 - May 09)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128344</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128344</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>With equal parts confident social observation and cutting self-deprecation, New York City-based comedian Brendan Sagalow has deftly and defiantly owned the stage for over 10 years. His debut full-hour comedy special, Thin Lips, was released in August 2024 on Youtube and continues to receive critical acclaim. Brendan performed as a “New Face” in the 2022 Just For Laughs Comedy Festival. He has also taken part in the Rogue Island Comedy Festival, Skankfest, and the New York Comedy Festival. He was a finalist in 2018’s New York’s Funniest, 2017’s Carolines Comedy Club Competition, and 2017’s Carolines March Madness Competition. He has written for MTV's Joking Off, and appeared on ViceTV’s Tumbleweeds with Killer Mike and the popular Barstool Sports series Answer the Internet. He is a recurring guest on The Jim and Sam Show, Barstool Sports’ KFC Radio, and The Bonfire with Big Jay Oakerson and Dan Soder. Brendan co-hosted Here’s the Scenario podcast with fellow comedians Mike Cannon and Mike Feeney, and now hosts his own show, Sagdaddy Da Pod. He has been a guest on a wide array of popular podcasts, including Are You Garbage?, Tuesdays with Stories, and Legion of Skanks. When not touring nationally, Brendan can be seen performing at clubs across New York City.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85553/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: KC Shornima (March 27 - March 29)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127883</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127883</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>KC is the newest Weekend Update writer on SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE. She previously was a staff writer on Comedy Central’s TOONING OUT THE NEWS and was selected as a Just For Laughs 2022 New Face in Montreal this past summer. KC has also performed at Just For Laughs Moontower, and alongside comedians Neal Brennan, Nate Bargatze and Dave Attell amongst others. KC was named the Best Up-and-Coming Comedian in Nashville by the Nashville Scene Magazine and was a semifinalist for STAND UP NBC. She has also written for and performed on Kevin Hart’s LOL Network.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/84746/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Colletti (March 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127880</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127880</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>With his natural charm and raw talent, Nick Colletti is quickly emerging as one of Hollywood’s most dynamic and sought-after comedians and personalities. Nick can currently be seen starring alongside Jimmy Tatro in Facebook Watch’s comedy-hit, THE REAL BROS OF SIMI VALLEY, which will soon begin production on it’s third season. Colletti stars as Duncan in the faux-reality show which centers on four best friends as they navigate life in Simi Valley. Online, Colletti has developed a massive fan base where he often posts videos and interacts with his 940k+ fans.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/32224/full/data?1621198831"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corey B (February 05 - February 07)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127878</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127878</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Corey Bonalewicz, aka COREY B, is an American radio personality, comedian, and content creator based in New York. Corey B has been working in Radio for over ten years. He got his start in New Orleans and has hosted radio shows in Chicago and New York. Prior to the pandemic, Corey performed stand up in the New York comedy club circuit and was planning on touring. Corey shifted his focus to long form content during the pandemic which showcased his comedic style on top of food hacks. He has amassed over 9M followers on TikTok and almost 6M followers on Facebook. He is releasing his own BBQ sauce and has equity in a New York restaurant and cookie company. Corey co-hosts a podcast, Cane and Corey, which is currently behind a paywall. He had a family YouTube page with his fiancé,The B Family, with a decent following but stopped posting due to restrictions on videos with children in them. Corey would like to dive back into YouTube and build upon this audience with a Corey B Reacts and Corey B Reviews page.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/65618/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Comedy N Dice (February 05)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127875</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127875</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A live role playing game where Tyler Wood and his fellow nerdy comedian friends take you on a one of a kind adventure. Will they succeed? Will they perish? Either way, you'll laugh until you 20 sided die!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/56756/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graeson McGaha (January 28)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127873</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127873</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Graeson McGaha is the feral force of comedy you didn’t know you needed. Hailing from the Southeast and raised on a steady diet of blue-collar grit and 90s chaos, Graeson has built a comedy brand that’s part stand-up, part southern storytelling, and part viral internet mayhem. Known to his fans as “the feral dad of Facebook,” Graeson weaves together tales of his coupon-clipping, craft-addicted wife, his Lord-of-the-Flies children, and the wild characters of small-town America with high-energy punchlines that hit harder than sweet tea at a church picnic.His shows are a mix of gut-punching laughter, southern-fried truth bombs, and a healthy dose of 80s/90s nostalgia. From “blue-collar bougie” parenting wisdom to feral family survival tactics, Graeson McGaha delivers a night of comedy that feels like you’re hanging out on the porch with your funniest, most unfiltered friend.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85832/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Ryan Goodcase (April 17 - April 19)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127431</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127431</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Praised for his smart writing and dry delivery, Ryan Goodcase became the youngest person to win the World Series of Comedy in 2019. Since then, he has also won the 45th San Francisco International Comedy Competition in 2021. You may also recognize him as the actor playing an apathetic Bed, Bath &amp; Beyond employee in a series of comedic online commercials. His debut comedy special, “Maybe They're Dead” was recently released via Tiny Pony. Most recently, Ryan can be seen in the 2024 Netflix is a Joke Fest's "Introducing,” a showcase of the next great talents in comedy.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/75732/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Carlino (March 19 - March 21)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127388</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127388</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Named the funniest person in Austin in 2023, Dylan Carlino is a hilariously funny comedian, writer and actor w/ a genuinely unique point of view. After beginning his career in the Berkshires, he spent several years in Portland, OR before moving to Austin, TX where he's quickly become one of the best comedians in the hottest comedy scene in the country. Dylan's been featured in multiple festivals including the Mass Moca Comedy Festival, the Moontower Comedy Festival and he was one of the new comics presented by Netflix is a Joke in their "Featuring..." showcase in 2024. Dylan also host's the podcast, SOME OF THIS IS BAD, w/ comedian Colton Dowling.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/82684/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manuel Angel Redondo EN ESPAÑOL (THIS SHOW IS COMPLETELY IN SPANISH WITH NO TRANSLATION) (March 14)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127385</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127385</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Manuel Ángel Redondo es un comediante y comunicador venezolano principalmente conocido por sus proyectos online como el webshow de sátira política Pero Tenemos Patria, el documental Viviendo al Mínimo o el muy exitoso programa de entrevistas alcoholizadas Entregrados. Hizo radio exitosamente en su país durante 10 años, hasta que fue forzado a salir del aire por los organismos de censura del gobierno venezolano. Desde ese entonces, hace comedia en Internet y por el mundo, con presentaciones agotadas por toda Europa, Latinoamérica y EEUU.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85177/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodnights Presents: Michael Colyar (March 13 - March 15)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127382</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127382</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>He is the multi-talented Michael Colyar, actor, comedian, and author. Michael is no stranger to work as he is still packing out shows in major cities night after night. His wit, charm and unique sense of style has been captivating audiences since the 80’s. Michael consistently performed every weekend, 5 shows a day on Venice Beach and was rightfully dubbed the “King of Venice Beach” while performing 9 years straight. His fans can’t get enough of him, “he’s real” “down to earth” “a giver”, they say. Michael’s philanthropic legacy extends beyond his $100K win from Star Search of which he gave 50% to the homeless. TodayMichael still finds the time to share laughter with those in need in shelters, rehabilitation centers, schools, and military bases. Michael Colyar is best known for his starring roles in Blackish, House Party III, Norbit, The Princess &amp; The Frog, and his role as Mr. Whitaker on the hit television series “Martin”. He is currently performing his one man play called “Michael COLYAR’S Momma” and will be launching a 100 plus city tour that has caught the attention of major television, cable, and streaming networks.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/24751/full/data?1563547811"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Improv 101 Graduation Showcase (February 19)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127292</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127292</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>EVER DREAM OF MAKING PEOPLE LAUGH? The Goodnights Comedy Academy is an ongoing monthly workshop which will focus on developing and honing an original stand-up routine. By the end of the month you will actually perform this act at the prestigious Goodnights Comedy Club! Our philosophy in teaching stand up is understanding that training is essential. Stand up comedy is an art form. It's a craft similar and not unlike any dance, theatre, or vocal program. There's a foundation that can be learned which will expedite one's success. Ongoing workshops are for everyone. Beginner to advanced. Interested? Click here for more information.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/77769/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Stand-up 101 Graduation Showcase (February 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127291</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127291</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>EVER DREAM OF MAKING PEOPLE LAUGH? The Goodnights Comedy Academy is an ongoing monthly workshop which will focus on developing and honing an original stand-up routine. By the end of the month you will actually perform this act at the prestigious Goodnights Comedy Club! Our philosophy in teaching stand up is understanding that training is essential. Stand up comedy is an art form. It's a craft similar and not unlike any dance, theatre, or vocal program. There's a foundation that can be learned which will expedite one's success. Ongoing workshops are for everyone. Beginner to advanced. Interested? Click here for more information.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/77766/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Wolf (March 05 - March 07)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127179</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127179</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Josh Wolf is a stand-up comedian, writer, actor, and New York Times best-selling author who has been entertaining audiences both on stage and on screen for over three decades. Wolf's comedy roots trace back to Boston and Seattle, eventually leading him to open for the likes of industry pillars such as Larry the Cable Guy and Chelsea Handler to name a few. After years of touring, writing, and performing, Josh has established himself as one of the most respected comedians in the industry, continuing to headline sold-out theaters across North America, Australia, New Zealand, and Europe. Wolf gained widespread acclaim as a comedian and panelist on the hit show ‘Chelsea Lately’ and as a mainstay performer on ‘After Lately’. He has since created, written, produced, and hosted shows like ‘The Josh Wolf Show’ and ‘Josh Wolf’s Wonderful World of Weird’. As a podcaster, Josh co-hosts the hit podcast “Hey Maaan” alongside his son, Jacob Wolf. The podcast is one of the only father-son collaborations in comedy, offering a unique perspective on family dynamics, life on the road, and trending topics. Wolf has also written and acted on hit shows like ‘My Name is Earl', ‘All of Us’, and ‘Raising Hope’. He was a regular panelist on the acclaimed comedy program ‘Lights Out with David Spade’ and has made numerous guest appearances on legendary programs such as ‘The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson’. As an author, Wolf penned the 2013 New York Times best-seller ‘It Takes Balls: Dating Single Moms and Other Confessions from an Unprepared Single Dad’. Fresh off the heels of his “High On Life Tour”, Wolf rolled out his most recent special, “The Campfire Special” which blends music and comedy and features an array of special guests. The special marked his fourth special in the past six years, further solidifying his prolific career and rabid fanbase. Wolf is currently wrapping his “Campfire Tour” through the end of 2025, hitting dozens of cities across the United States before embarking with a brand new hour in 2026. In addition to touring, Wolf has a weekly residency at Jimmy Kimmel’s Comedy Club in Las Vegas where he performs every Monday to a packed house. Leveraging his strong presence on social media and YouTube, Wolf has amassed over 7.4 million followers across platforms and more than 280 million views on his YouTube channel alone, continuing to further expand his reach and deepen his connection with fans.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85414/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Steve Hofstetter &amp; Friends (August 09)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127087</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127087</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Author, columnist, and comedian Steve Hofstetter is often called the hardest working man in show-business. With all due respect to the late James Brown. Hofstetter's national TV debut came on ESPN's Quite Frankly, where Stephen A. Smith yelled at him for three minutes. Hofstetter has also appeared on CBS' "Late Late Show With Craig Ferguson", Showtime's "White Boyz in the Hood", VH1's "Countdown", Sundance's "On the Road in America", and ABC's "Barbara Walter's Special", where he thankfully did not cry. He is the host and executive producer of "Laughs" on Fox networks, where he only cries occasionally. One of the top booked acts on the college circuit, the original writer for collegehumor.com has also released six albums. Hofstetter has written humor columns for the New York Times, SportsIllustrated.com, and NHL.com, where he publicly admitted to being a Ranger fan. After hosting Four Quotas on Sirius Satellite Radio for two seasons, Hofstetter moved to broadcast radio, and his Sports Minute (Or So) was syndicated on over 170 stations and in over 30 newspapers. Hofstetter's second live comedy album ("Cure For the Cable Guy") reached #20 on Billboard's comedy charts. His third album ("Dark Side of the Room") was the first ever pay-what-you-want" comedy album, since people were going to steal it anyway. His fourth album consisted of an hour of 100% ad-libbed material, which is, frankly, nuts. And his fifth album hit #1 on iTunes' comedy charts, which is also a bit nuts. Hofstetter's brutal tour schedule consists of over 100 colleges and dozens of clubs every year, and is fueled by an immense online popularity, tons of press, and a Prius with great gas mileage. He reached 200,000 friends on Facebook and 400,000 more on MySpace, and high shelves in grocery stores. While Hofstetter's live shows are routinely sold out, he is best known for his writing, first published at age 15, mainly to impress girls. At 18, he co-founded "Sports Jerk of the Week", an irreverent website featured by press like USA Today's Baseball Weekly, Sports Illustrated and CNN. And at 20, Hofstetter took a year off of school to head up web content for the New York Yankees. The Yankees won the World Series that year, which would have been wonderful if they hadn't beaten Hofstetter's Mets. Yes, he's also a Mets fan. Poor kid. While an undergraduate at Columbia University, Hofstetter was a well-read columnist for the Columbia Daily Spectator and a voice of the Lions. After a summer writing for Maxim, ESPN, and Sports Illustrated for Kids, Hofstetter syndicated his column in several newspapers. Without his glasses, Hofstetter also looks a great deal like Michael Rappaport.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/41826/full/data?1652279902"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Peyton Ruddy (February 26 - February 28)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127086</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/127086</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Peyton Ruddy, known most initially for going viral on the hit podcast, Kill Tony, has begun to blow up on social media with his daily bizarre circumstances. He started stand up in the suburbs of Chicago at 17 years old and quickly grew in popularity to become a favorite in the city. He recently moved to Austin, Texas and has been referred to as “cutesy wootsey fat shit.” Peyton has opened for names such as Tim Dillon, Ron White, Chris Distefano, Ari Shaffir, Craig Robinson, Harland Williams, Bret Ernst, Steph Tolev, Sam Tallent, and Casey Rocket, all while still maintaining his rockin’ hot bod.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/81566/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Santi Espinosa (January 29)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126883</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126883</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Based in NEW YORK CITY, Santi is a multilingual stand-up comedian who is taking his show on tour this year. He has been doing standup comedy for over a decade and his comedy can be described as honest, anecdotal and personal. He is the host of the very successful comedy showcase ItMatters Comedy at New York Comedy Club. He has performed from small and big audiences in rundown bars/comedy clubs across North America to sold out clubs in London, England and Bogota, Colombia. Santi is one of the few comics who has performed at the New York Comedy Festival both in English and Spanish. His debut comedy album IDENTITY CRISIS can be listened to on iTunes, Sirius XM and Spotify. He also did a commercial with famous actor Will Arnett and some of his credits Include: NY Comedy Festival, TBS, and Sirius/XM.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85252/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Think Not! Live (February 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126766</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126766</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Ellyn Marsh and Joey Taranto are bringing their hit true crime / comedy podcast “I Think Not!” to the stage! Join them on tour as they recap an episode of one of their (and your!) favorite true-crime TV shows. Ellyn and Joey are long-time friends from performing together on Broadway, so they’re obsessed with each other, trash TV, and all things true crime. Expect their signature mix of humor and heart (and let’s be honest, they will probably randomly break out into song) as they break down one of the wackiest cases from the best true crime series that campy television has to offer!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/62474/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gianmarco Soresi (May 14 - May 16)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126763</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126763</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Gianmarco Soresi is a New York-based stand-up comedian, actor, and creator known for his sharp societal observation and spry, energetic stage presence. Gianmarco effortlessly commands a room with his animated style, blending upbeat candor with dark comedic beats, which has garnered him critical acclaim from The New York Times, NPR, Esquire, The Atlantic, Buzzfeed, ABC News, Billboard, and many more. He’s performed stand-up on The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon, The Late Late Show with James Corden, Comedy Central, Don’t Tell, and was selected as a JFL New Face in 2022. He has amassed a dedicated following of millions across social media accounts and is the host of the popular podcast “The Downside with Gianmarco Soresi. Gianmarco released his first hour-long special, THIEF OF JOY, which reached over 1 million views in the first week and counting.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85176/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clare Bowen &amp; Jonathan Jackson (May 19)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126761</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126761</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Before landing the iconic role of Scarlett O'Connor on the ABC/CMT/HULU TV series NASHVILLE, and launching her career as a singer/songwriter, Clare Bowen was growing up in rural Australia. Bowen heard her first broadcast of the Grand Ole Opry on the wireless in her grandad’s kitchen and soon after, her classical vocal coach paused one of their lessons to comment on the "country lilt" that had naturally crept into Bowen's voice. It would be another decade before she'd duet with heavyweights like Zac Brown and Vince Gill, recording songs with GRAMMY-winning producers like T-Bone Burnett and Buddy Miller who became her mentors. She released an eponymous album and performed before soldout crowds in the US, UK, Germany and Australia. She also earned a coveted spot on Sugarland’s “Still The Same” tour and toured live with the Nashville cast, selling out London’s O2 Arena. Alongside the spotlight, Clare is no stranger to the darker more frightening side of the human experience. A pediatric cancer survivor, she was given just two weeks to live upon receiving a shocking cancer diagnosis at age four. With the strength of her family behind her, she survived a grueling chemotherapy regimen and is now known around the world as a beautiful ray of sunshine who leads with her heart, able to communicate and translate emotions whether on stage or on screen. Now half of the duo known as BOWEN * YOUNG, she and her husband, Brandon Robert Young are releasing music that masterfully delves into the depths of ferocious love, heartbreaking loss and steadfast hope. They have dubbed the music “Cinematic Americana”, and their debut album, “Us”, was released in May 2024 and available everywhere. Join Jonathan Jackson, musician, actor, author and filmmaker for an afternoon of live music, poetry, and stories Live on Stage at the Comedy Vault. Jonathan, best known for his role as "Lucky Spencer" on General Hospital and "Avery Barkley" on the drama series Nashville, brings his talents to the stage to engage with his fans in an intimate show with songs from Nashville, music from his new album, original poetry, and behind the scenes stories. There will also be time for a Q&amp;A session!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85184/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Shaun Jones (January 16 - January 18)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126759</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126759</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>When Shaun Jones hits the stage, the room shifts. This New Jersey native has spent the last 30 years dominating the comedy circuit with a signature blend of sharp wit, real-life storytelling, and electrifying stage presence. His performance isn't just a show – it's an experience. Authentic. Unfiltered. Laugh-out-loud unforgettable. Audiences nationwide know Shaun from the viral Allied Injury Group commercials as "Your Favorite Attorney," but his résumé runs deep. He's been featured on BET's Comic View, Starz 1st Amendment Stand-Up, Robert Townsend's Partners in Crime, The Mo'Nique Show, and appeared in the feature film Shade alongside Jamie Foxx and Sylvester Stallone. He's also showcased his dramatic range on ID-TV's Your Worst Nightmare. Onstage, Shaun doesn't just tell jokes – he commands every moment. His natural charisma, veteran timing, and fearless honesty leave crowds laughing, talking, and coming back for more. If you're ready for a night of comedy you'll still be quoting next week, you need to see Shaun Jones live. This isn't just another comedy – it's the one you'll brag about.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85175/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Dru Montana (April 30)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126424</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126424</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The reigning, defending champion of the Preble Frog Pulls, Dru has been doing comedy in Philadelphia for over 6 years. Known from being a regular at Skankfest, or his appearances on Matt and Shane's Secret Podcast, Tuesdays with Stories, and Story Warz, along with his two hit podcasts, Durag and the Deertag and the prank call show, Digital Bazooka. He can also do 100 push ups. This is guaranteed to be the best time of your life.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85043/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Cold &amp; The Jackal (February 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126417</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/126417</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Steve Burton and Bradford Anderson play the roles of Jason Morgan and Damian Spinelli on ABC's soap opera, "General Hospital." Fans love their unique friendship on screen, but their real-life dynamic is perhaps even more entertaining. In addition to their long-running podcast and entertaining their legions of fans on social media, Steve and Bradford are touring all over the country to the delight of GH fans everywhere. Join them for a 75 minute show full of music and comedy followed by a limited VIP photo meet and greet. Bring your own camera, no autographs</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83953/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Murray (June 04 - June 06)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125980</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125980</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>James Murray is a writer, executive producer, and actor, best known as “Murr” on the hit television show Impractical Jokers on truTV. He is also one of the stars of the TV show The Misery Index on TBS along with his comedy troupe, The Tenderloins. He has worked as the Senior Vice President of Development for NorthSouth Productions for a decade, is the owner of Impractical Productions, LLC, and is the author of the international bestselling novels Awakened and The Brink. Originally from Staten Island, he now lives in Princeton, NJ.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/71420/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martin Amini (May 07 - May 09)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125979</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125979</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Martin Amini is a standup comic based in Los Angeles, California and born and raised in Silver Spring, Maryland. Martin draws comedic inspiration from his diverse heritage, crafting a unique blend of humor that resonates universally. Growing up with an Iranian father and a Bolivian mother, Martin's multicultural background provides rich material for his stand-up routines, creating an engaging comedic experience. In addition to exploring his heritage, Martin infuses his comedy with insights from his own experiences of marriage, offering hilarious commentary on relationships that audiences can personally relate to. Moreover, Martin occasionally plays matchmaker on stage, helping audience members find love amidst the laughter. Beyond his work on stage, Martin is also the Founder of Room 808, a vibrant comedian run comedy club located in Washington DC. Currently, he is embarking on a three-continent tour, showcasing his distinctive brand of comedy to audiences worldwide.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85103/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Emma Willmann (April 17 - April 19)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125978</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125978</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Emma Willmann is a stand-up comedian, actress, and podcaster originally from Blue Hill, Maine. A comic who’s mastered chaos under control, Willmann’s vibrant presence, warmth, and unflinching honesty make her a comedian to be reckoned with. She was a part of the inaugural season of Netflix’s The Lineup, and has made memorable appearances in CW’s Crazy Ex-Girlfriend, Judd Apatow’s Crashing and The Good Fight on Paramount+. Willmann has also made multiple appearances on The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, and is a regular at the prestigious Comedy Cellar in New York City.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/84664/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Damon Darling (March 08)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125977</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125977</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>With about a million social media followers Damon Darling has over 18 million page likes on TikTok alone for his drive thru pranks and standup comedy clips! He has opened for some of the biggest names and is now headlining his own tour and selling out shows! Mixing jokes with his true life stories and crowd working the audience off the top of the head makes Damon Darling an exciting and very entertainingly funny comedian to watch!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/58110/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Anthony Fuentes (January 22 - January 24)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125862</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Anthony Fuentes, a Chicago-based stand-up comedian originally from Brooklyn, NY, began his comedy journey in 2011 while bartending in Chicago, using humor as a therapeutic outlet to cope with PTSD. Inspired by legends like Eddie Murphy, Richard Pryor, and George Carlin, he developed a sharp storytelling style infused with truth, humor, and nostalgia, drawing from his experiences in the ’80s and ’90s, fatherhood, and everyday life. As a U.S. Armed Forces veteran, Anthony channels his discipline and resilience into his performances, captivating audiences nationwide. He has headlined top clubs including Zanies, The Comedy Cellar, and The Laugh Factory, toured major cities from Las Vegas to New York, and shared the stage with Mark Viera, Ralph Barbosa, and Ken Flores. Featured on WGN, he recently wrapped his debut comedy special My Way, now in post-production, and continues to bring his signature energy to stages across the country.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83562/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Helium Track Stars Album Recording "Eat it" (January 29)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125715</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125715</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>“Track Stars” is a recurring comedy showcase that doubles as a live recording session for Helium’s record label, Helium Tracks. Each month spotlights a new theme, with a rotating cast of comedians crafting material tailored to that concept. Join us for the creation of a new compilation album bound for the Helium Tracks catalogue and Sirius XM! It’s part stand‑up show, part studio session and all around a chance to see top‑tier comics record unique sets in an intimate, energetic environment.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/82497/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Antoniou (February 18)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125514</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125514</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Peter Antoniou fuses his amazing and uncanny ability to read minds with razor sharp wit, story telling, and improvisational comedy to create unique live entertainment experiences. From London’s West End to America’s Got Talent, he has become an international sensation, presenting his remarkable and hilarious shows for sell-out theatre audiences, comedy clubs, blue chip companies, and royalty.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/81565/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocky Dale Davis (March 11)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125511</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125511</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Rocky Dale Davis is a nationally touring comedian who has appeared on NBC’s “Bring The Funny”, E’s “Dating No Filter” and MTV’s “Greatest Party Stories.”</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/31733/full/data?1618652650"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geoffrey Asmus (March 26)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125442</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125442</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Geoffrey Asmus began performing stand-up in 2013 immediately after wasting $143,548 on seven college degrees. Geoffrey has performed at ‘ Just For Laughs in Montreal as a ‘New Face’ and was also featured on FOX’s ‘Laughs’, CollegeHumor and Kevin Hart’s LOL Network. Geoffrey has opened for Dave Attell, Mark Normand, Dan Soder, Fortune Feimster, Sam Morrill, Daniel Sloss, Joe List and Aparna Nancherla among others. He headlines comedy clubs nationwide. In 2021 he released his first album “Prodigal Little Bitch” through 800 Lb Gorilla Records and it went to #1 on iTunes. Geoffrey also records the weekly Youre An Idiot podcast with Alex Dragicevich. It is the only funny podcast in America. But no matter where he performs Geoffrey never makes eye contact, which is a blessing for all.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/39344/full/data?1645047463"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Bo Johnson (February 20 - February 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125440</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125440</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Bo Johnson is a comedian from Seattle, Washington. He can be found headlining clubs, breweries, and dingy bars across the United States and sometimes Canada. His stand up was featured on season two of Kevin Hart Presents: Hart of the City on Comedy Central. The following summer Bo taped a set for LOL Live! at the prestigious Just For Laughs comedy festival in Montreal. He was a finalist in the 39th annual Seattle International Comedy Competition and is a regular at festivals including Bumbershoot, SF Sketchfest, the Double Down Comedy Experience sponsored by Zappos, Life is Beautiful in Las Vegas, and Big Pine Comedy Festival in Phoenix. TikTok user stichpool626 said about Bo: "You have this... quality about you. Like Chandler, from Friends. lol. "</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/48119/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoltan Kaszas (April 23 - April 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125136</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125136</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Zoltan Kaszas is a Hungarian-born, award-winning stand-up comedian known for his sharp, observational humor. Kaszas, who The Atlantic called a “breakout star,” has been featured on several SiriusXM comedy channels, Laughs on Fox, Netflix Is a Joke, Scotland’s Fringe Festival and headlines comedy clubs and theaters across the country. It was his riff on why cats are better than dogs that brought viral fame, racking up over 68 million views with The Guardian’s (UK) calling it one of the “ten funniest things I’ve seen on the Internet.” Kaszas has two Dry Bar standup specials and four independent standup specials on YouTube: Modern Male, White Lies, Honorary Jones and his most recent, London Fog. His ability to take relatable experiences and turn them into hilarious stories has earned him both critical acclaim and a loyal following.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/63633/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drew Lynch (March 27 - March 29)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125067</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125067</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Comedian and actor Drew Lynch captured the hearts of America with his Golden Buzzer performance on Season 10 of America’s Got Talent (NBC), where he finished in second place. Since then, Drew has amassed millions of followers on social media while touring the world nonstop to sold out audiences. In February 2023, Drew released his second special ‘And These Are Jokes’ which is catching steam all over the internet. He also appeared in a recurring role in the final season of IFC’s hit series Maron as well as TBS’ Conan. A favorite on the podcast circuit, Drew has made multiple appearances on some of the most downloaded shows, giving his unique take on everything from pop culture to news headlines to the life of a traveling comic.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/30815/full/data?1612996420"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher's Night Out With Gaspare Randazzo (February 01)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125039</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125039</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Gaspare Randazzo is a teacher entering his 11th year in the classroom. When he’s not in the classroom, you can find him doing stand-up comedy where he talks about his life as a teacher and his experiences dealing with students from all walks of life. His stories range from students hating him and wanting to punch him in the face to them loving him and bringing him school lunch trays to eat during every period. These non-conventional stories will have teachers and all others alike finding themselves laughing and scratching their heads at just how outrageous they are!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/43132/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Chris Porter (March 12 - March 14)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125038</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125038</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Best known for his third place finish on the season 4 of Last Comic Standing. Chris can also be seen on his own “Comedy Central Presents” special and “Live at Gotham”. Chris Porter has been a touring comic since he was 23. Since the beginning Chris’ raw energy and unique perspective has distinguished him as one of the elite comics in the industry. Born and raised in Kansas City, Chris brings a true stand-up experience to his live shows. There are no sound cues, no puppets, and no catch phrases. Just gut wrenching laughter drawn from his own experience and observations.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/30786/full/data?1612972835"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentine's Weekend With Caleb Elliott (February 13 - February 15)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125037</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125037</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Caleb Elliott is a comedian, writer and actor from North Carolina. He has been performing stand up since he was 11 years old. He started his comedy career at Goodnights Comedy Club and first opened for Bill Bellamy at age 14. Caleb has worked with comedians such as Tracey Morgan, Ralphie May, Donnell Rawlings and in 2019 had the pleasure of touring with the legendary comedian Sinbad. In 2020 he became the youngest comic to release a Dry Bar Comedy Special, “Diary of a Smooth Black Kid.” In 2021 he released a comedy extended playlist “Humorous Interpretation” on Sirius XM and Laugh USA. He is currently on tour with comedian John Crist.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/82074/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Ladanye (February 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125036</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/125036</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Jason Ladanye is a professional, award-winning sleight-of-hand entertainer who has performed card magic all around the world for the last twenty years. Jason exposes the underground world of cheating at cards and how to beat Las Vegas if you have the skills. He has spent a lifetime mastering this skill set and it’s an experience your guests will never forget.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/65867/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Cocoa Brown (January 30 - February 01)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124935</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124935</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Most notably known for her lead role in Tyler Perry's The Single Mom's Club and For Better or Worse, the hilarious comedian/actress Cocoa (pronounced Co-kah) Brown treats audiences to thought-provoking humor in which she declares “I don’t tell jokes I tell the truth!” Her Grown Woman delivery both on stage and on the screen in supporting roles such as FX's American Crime Story, NBC's Marlon, and most recently FOX's critically acclaimed 9-1-1, has generated a large and loyal following all over the world and has proven to her fans old and new that not only is she a funny comedian but she is also a versatile actress. Cocoa has had guest star roles on several other notable TV projects including 2 Broke Girls, Psych, The Soul Man, and Breaking Bad as well as supporting roles in Ted 2, in which she was hand-picked for the role of "Joy" by Seth MacFarlane, and Lakeview Terrace with Samuel L. Jackson. Being appropriately dubbed as a "comedy machine gun" by America's Got Talent judge Sharon Osbourne, she has received numerous awards including the DC Comedian of the Year after only a short time of stand-up and was hand picked by the family of Moms Mabley to receive the 2018 Moms Mabley Legacy Award. She is a fan favorite and has been all over the world touring regularly and has also been featured on the Showtime Network Shaquille O'Neal Comedy All-Stars. Not only do audiences get a great show but they feel as though they have gained a friend. Cocoa says, "If my audience feels like they know me, then that means I've connected with them and I've shared my gift." Cocoa has a style that relates to both women and men and an energy and warmness on and off the stage that has earned her the respect and love of crowds and colleagues alike.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/29273/full/data?1596662851"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brittany Schmitt (January 27)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124934</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124934</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Brittany Schmitt is an LA-based, Wisconsin-raised comic. She likes her comedy like she likes her cheese: stanky. Don’t be fooled by her girl-next-door looks, her humor is insidious and unapologetic. She’s been featured in clubs across the country opening for Theo Von, Chris Redd and more. She was just on Comedy Central’s "Stand-Up Featuring", Don’t Tell Comedy: Backyard Series and just put out her debut comedy special: From Ho to Housewife with 800 Pound Gorilla on July 19th, with many of the clips hitting over 10M+ views.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/51191/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carter Anderson (January 14)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124933</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124933</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Carter Anderson is a comedian, social creator, and actor originally from San Antonio but now in New York. He got his start in Theatre and Radio before deciding to sling jokes full time. You may have also seen his hilarious videos on Tiktok or Instagram with his characters yelling “That Is Not Your Slogan, Beetch!!!” or his recent Dry Bar standup special. Carter has won the House Of Hyjinx Comedy Competition and the Western Oregon Comedy Competition, and came in Second in the Comedy vs. Tragedy Competition. Carter was named “One of The Indisputable Geniuses Of Comedy” by The Portland Mercury Magazine in 2018. He was selected to perform at the 2021 San Francisco Sketchiest and has also appeared in an episode of Portlandia and Epix original comedy doc-series, Unprotected Sets.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83781/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Liz Miele (January 09 - January 11)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124932</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Liz Miele is a NYC comedian who has appeared on Comedy Central, FOX, AXS TV, Hulu, NPR’s Wait Wait Don’t Tell Me and CBS’s After Midnight. She's been featured in The New Yorker, NY Times, Runner's World, Psychology Today and The Guardian. She has several viral videos on YouTube, Instagram and TikTok including jokes “Feminist Sex Positions,” "Dating Is Harder for Comedians," and "F*ck Finland". She regularly tours internationally and has five albums with a combined 6+ million views on youtube. Her last special was listed on the New York Times, Paste Magazine and Interrobang “Best Comedy Specials of 2022” list. Her new special “Murder Sheets” premiered April of 2024. Her book "Why Cats Are A**holes" was published March 2021. She has a weekly podcast with comedian Maria Shehata called 2 Non-Doctors. For more info visit her website: www.lizmiele.com</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/58519/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodnights Presents: DC Curry (January 09 - January 11)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124699</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124699</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Don “D.C.” Curry’s talents are far more than meets the eye at a single glance. At second glance you’ll see him co-starring in major studio pictures or taking on the duties of the leading man in indie feature films. Look again and you’ll see him touring the country as the lead in a hit stage play or serving as the front man of his own R&amp;B and Blues band. Take yet another glimpse (or listen) and you’ll hear him shining as a skilled voice-over artist on hit TV shows like Boondocks. Bottom line, DC Curry is a very versatile, and extremely funny man.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/64886/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Jeselnik (February 19 - February 21)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124360</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124360</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Anthony Jeselnik is a critically acclaimed stand-up comedian. Over the past 25 years, he has performed all across the globe and has written, produced, and starred in three Netflix comedy specials: Thoughts and Prayers, Fire in the Maternity Ward, and his latest, Bones and All. Jeselnik also wrote, produced, and starred in the comedy special Caligula and the stand-up album Shakespeare. In addition to his stand-up, Jeselnik is an Emmy-nominated writer who created, produced, and starred in the cult-classic television series Good Talk with Anthony Jeselnik and The Jeselnik Offensive, alongside his breakout performances on The Roast of Donald Trump and The Roast of Charlie Sheen.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83560/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Nasso (May 06)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124351</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124351</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Austin Nasso is a New York-based comedian and impressionist who left a career as a Microsoft software engineer to pursue comedy full-time. He is a recurring guest performer on the Howard Stern Show and the co founder of the internationally touring Tech Roast Show. Known for his tech-savvy humor and impeccable impressions, Austin has amassed a following of over 2 million online since he began performing comedy at age 15.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83737/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Normand (May 01 - May 02)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124234</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124234</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Dubbed by Jerry Seinfeld as the “best young up and coming comic,” Mark Normand has quickly become one of the most talked about touring comedians on the scene. Normand’s 2023 one- hour Netflix special, SOUP TO NUTS, was a staple in the streamers’ Top Ten for several weeks. This follows Normand’s self-released special, 2020’s OUT TO LUNCH which amassed over 12 million views on YouTube. He also starred on Netflix’s Season 3 of THE STAND UPS. Normand’s popularity has also translated to tours internationally to such countries as Australia, New Zealand, United Kingdom, Spain, Norway and Portugal. An extremely prolific stand-up, the New Orleans born comedian previously had two Comedy Central specials and has made an unparalleled seven appearances on “Conan,” four appearances on “The Tonight Show with Jimmy Fallon,” and has also appeared on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert.” Mark is a frequent guest on “The Joe Rogan Experience,” and hosts his own podcasts “Tuesdays with Stories” and “We Might Be Drunk.”</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83736/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarper Guven (January 21 - January 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124072</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/124072</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Born and raised in Turkey, now lost in the madness of America. Sarper brings his sharp, hilarious takes on marriage, jealousy, and the wild cultural differences between Turkish and American life. With fresh observations about living in the U.S., he’s here to prove that laughter is universal.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/82502/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trae Crowder (April 16 - April 19)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123874</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123874</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Trae Crowder first gained international attention (or notoriety depending on your politics) in 2016 for his hugely viral series of “Liberal Redneck” comedic “porch rant” videos. Since then, Trae has written a best-selling book, The Liberal Redneck Manifesto: Draggin Dixie Outta The Dark, toured the country thrice over playing sold out theatre shows under the WellRED Comedy Tour banner, appeared on Real Time with Bill Maher (HBO), Nightline (ABC), The View, Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell (MSNBC), NPR, WTF with Marc Maron, MTV, CNN, Huffington Post and in the Veronica Mars reboot, as “Chattanooga Charlie”, among many others. Initially from rural Celina, TN, Trae now lives in Los Angeles, CA and has developed and sold five scripted pilots for Warner Bros TV, ABC, and FOX and continues to work as a writer. Trae stars in and produces regular sketches for Comedy Central, Funny or Die, ATTN, Facebook Watch, New York Daily News which have garnered tens of millions of views online. Crowder also co-wrote and produced an hour-long documentary titled Inherent Good, featuring Crowder and former presidential candidate Andrew Yang, about universal basic income. Additionally, Trae co-hosts the hugely popular “WellRED,” “Evening Skews” and “Puttin’ On Airs” podcasts. His debut 30-minute standup comedy special was taped in 2021 in Nashville, TN and his latest full-length special “Trash Daddy” is available now on YouTube. He also continues to rant and rave on the internet to the mostly-delight of his lovely fanbase.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85550/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masood Boomgaard (January 20)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123725</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123725</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Self-help Singh is the alter ego of international comedian Masood Boomgaard. Self-help Singh, described as a comedic alternative life coach and de-motivational speaker, first appeared to Boomgaard in a vision after he fell and hit his head while rushing to the bathroom in an attempt to outrun the gastric consequences of bad lamb vindaloo. Boomgaard has since been sharing the "common sense wisdom" and de-motivational teachings of Self-help Singh to millions of people on the internet. The Self-help Singh live show is a hilarious yet thought-provoking juxtaposition of stand-up comedy, parody and motivational speaking. During his decade-long full-time professional comedy career Boomgaard has performed in New York, London, Dubai and during the lockdown, in his father's garage. He lives in South Africa with his cat...for now.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/58487/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelly Belly (March 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123355</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/123355</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Shelly Belly has taken the comedy and social media scene by storm. Shelly Belly has become one of the top sought after female comedians throughout the United States delighting fans with her hilarious standup comedy. Michelle has branched out, taking her quick wit comedy routine from her front porch of South Carolina to the main stage traveling throughout the United States. Michelle’s relatable comedy consists of saying the things that we all think about and want to say it. Shelly began her comedy career performing contagious everyday comedy on stages across the Southeast gaining attention in the comedy world. Michelle’s career took off after releasing her comedy skits “Shelly Belly Comedy” online earning her millions of views on social media platforms as ‘Shelly Belly’. Studio Lambert discovered Shelly Belly AKA Michelle Rider on her social media platforms and chose her to be on the number one reality show “The Circle” Season 3 on Netflix. Shelly has been featured in Entertainment Tonight, NBC, Fox, Parade, Screen Rant, Stars Offline, Women's Health, Yahoo News, Decider, Men's Health, IMDb</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/69191/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Chris Higgins (July 10 - July 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/122855</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/122855</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Chris Higgins is a nationally touring comedian from Colorado, now based in Chicago, who brings a unique blend of stoner wisdom, masterful impressions, and outdoorsy sensibilities to stages across the country. Known for his viral stand-up clips that have amassed millions of views, his online sketch series "God n Angel" (1.6M followers), and his comedy special "Live at the Fort," Chris is quickly establishing himself as one of comedy's most distinctive rising voices. A festival favorite, Chris has performed at the New York Comedy Festival, Netflix is a Joke Comedy Festival, and High Plains Comedy Festival, while taking home "Best of the Fest" honors at both Westend Comedy Festival and 10,000 Laughs Comedy Festival. His comedy has been featured on Don't Tell Comedy, ViceTV, Bob &amp; Tom, and he's currently selling out stops nationwide. Chris's comedy attracts fans of comics like Rory Scovel, Kyle Kinane, and Mitch Hedberg - audiences who appreciate clever wordplay, unexpected perspectives, and a comedian who proves you can be both laid-back and razor-sharp. Chris combines Colorado's outdoor spirit with Chicago's comedy hustle to create something entirely his own. Chris would list more credits, but it's generally frowned upon to claim you're the host of the Tonight Show without being Jimmy Fallon.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/83082/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akaash Singh (February 26 - February 28)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/122043</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/122043</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Akaash Singh is a nationally touring stand up comedian, podcaster, and actor. His career took off with many television shows including MTV’s “Guy Code” and “Wild’n Out,” Netflix’s “Brown Nation,” and HBO’s “The Leftovers” After finding success in TV, he pivoted his focus toward growing the now hugely successful podcast “Flagrant,” co-created with fellow comedian and good friend, Andrew Schulz, along with touring and pop his stand up career. Akaash self-produced and directed his first stand up special, “Bring Back Apu” in February, amassing over a million views in its first week alone. Just one month later, he released “The Crowdwork Special,” putting him in rarified air of comedians who produced two specials in back to back months. Aside from stand up, look for Akaash as the lead in the Netflix Animated Series "Conquest" as well as a Hulu series created by Ramy Youssef.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/50630/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Rapaport (March 05 - March 07)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121987</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121987</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Michael Rapaport is an American actor and comedian. He has appeared in over sixty films since the early 1990s, and starred on the sitcom The War at Home. He also appeared in Boston Public, Friends, Prison Break, Justified, and Atypical. Some of his notable film roles include True Romance (1993), Higher Learning (1995), Metro (1997), Cop Land (1997), Deep Blue Sea (1999), The 6th Day (2000), Dr. Dolittle 2 (2001), Big Fan (2009), and The Heat (2013). He also directed the award winning documentary Beats, Rhymes &amp; Life: The Travels of a Tribe Called Quest (2011).” He’s also the host of the world wide phenomenon “I Am Rapaport Stereo Podcast.”</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/57324/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Cousin Tiera (January 15)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121983</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121983</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Tiera is a standup comedian born and raised on the west side of Chicago, Illinois. She’s known for making the world laugh via her viral videos on Facebook and Instagram. She is more than just an Internet sensation. From the first time she touched the mic in 2016, she’s been rocking shows across the globe. She takes pride in her raw and relatable comedy and she’s a great storyteller. She has shared the stage with a variety of established comedians such as Damon Williams, Bill Bellamy, Melanie Cormacho, TK Kirkland, etc. In 2022, she advanced as a FINALIST with outstanding numbers in Kenan Thompson’s “Road to New York” comedy competition and the list goes on. Additionally, in 2022, she made her featured debut in an upcoming film titled “Comedy Lights The Dark!”. Her relatability and catchy phrases are guaranteed to make you laugh.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/53822/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And Then We Had Sex (January 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121589</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121589</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>If you weren't aware, "And Then We Had Sex" is possibly the fastest growing podcast in your area! Each week, married couple and show hosts, comedian Kristen Sivills and writer J-Rod Tanner guide you into their unconventional world of sex, comedy, and uninhibited truth. Kristen has toured nationally with acts such as Anjelah Johnson, Tone Bell, and was one of the headliners for Wendy Williams, and Summer Theatre Tour, to name a few. J-Rod has written and worked with numerous comedians and actors including his partner, Jay Pharoah. Their hilarious takes on relationships, uncensored interviews, insightful and open sex talk, and willingness to put the spotlight on the most personal parts of their marriage will leave you laughing, blushing, and binging every single episode! Reaching more than 30 countries and amassing over thousands of weekly streams and downloads, this is the one podcast that you MUST subscribe to, whether you’re a regular pod listener or you’re interested in losing your pod-ginity!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/54495/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dustin Nickerson (January 29 - January 31)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121437</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/121437</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A Seattle native now suffering in Southern California, Dustin Nickerson is an in demand comic on the rise. In addition to being recently featured on Comedy Central and Netflix by Kevin Hart, he’s been seen Fox, the Grand Ole Opry’s Circle Network, the PBS Comedy Hour, Hulu, contributed to the Huffington Post and can regularly be heard on Sirius Radio XM. Dustin describes himself as “the world’s most average person” but is far from it when on stage. He brings you into his life through his jokes about the struggles of parenting, marriage, and being generally annoyed by most people. At just 35 years old, Dustin has been married for 15 years and has three kids! This helps makes Dustin truly one of the most unique voices in the comedy scene.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/40239/full/data?1647646986"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Hofstetter (May 03)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/118372</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/118372</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:16:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Author, columnist, and comedian Steve Hofstetter is often called the hardest working man in show-business. With all due respect to the late James Brown. Hofstetter's national TV debut came on ESPN's Quite Frankly, where Stephen A. Smith yelled at him for three minutes. Hofstetter has also appeared on CBS' "Late Late Show With Craig Ferguson", Showtime's "White Boyz in the Hood", VH1's "Countdown", Sundance's "On the Road in America", and ABC's "Barbara Walter's Special", where he thankfully did not cry. He is the host and executive producer of "Laughs" on Fox networks, where he only cries occasionally. One of the top booked acts on the college circuit, the original writer for collegehumor.com has also released six albums. Hofstetter has written humor columns for the New York Times, SportsIllustrated.com, and NHL.com, where he publicly admitted to being a Ranger fan. After hosting Four Quotas on Sirius Satellite Radio for two seasons, Hofstetter moved to broadcast radio, and his Sports Minute (Or So) was syndicated on over 170 stations and in over 30 newspapers. Hofstetter's second live comedy album ("Cure For the Cable Guy") reached #20 on Billboard's comedy charts. His third album ("Dark Side of the Room") was the first ever pay-what-you-want" comedy album, since people were going to steal it anyway. His fourth album consisted of an hour of 100% ad-libbed material, which is, frankly, nuts. And his fifth album hit #1 on iTunes' comedy charts, which is also a bit nuts. Hofstetter's brutal tour schedule consists of over 100 colleges and dozens of clubs every year, and is fueled by an immense online popularity, tons of press, and a Prius with great gas mileage. He reached 200,000 friends on Facebook and 400,000 more on MySpace, and high shelves in grocery stores. While Hofstetter's live shows are routinely sold out, he is best known for his writing, first published at age 15, mainly to impress girls. At 18, he co-founded "Sports Jerk of the Week", an irreverent website featured by press like USA Today's Baseball Weekly, Sports Illustrated and CNN. And at 20, Hofstetter took a year off of school to head up web content for the New York Yankees. The Yankees won the World Series that year, which would have been wonderful if they hadn't beaten Hofstetter's Mets. Yes, he's also a Mets fan. Poor kid. While an undergraduate at Columbia University, Hofstetter was a well-read columnist for the Columbia Daily Spectator and a voice of the Lions. After a summer writing for Maxim, ESPN, and Sports Illustrated for Kids, Hofstetter syndicated his column in several newspapers. Without his glasses, Hofstetter also looks a great deal like Michael Rappaport.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/41826/full/data?1652279902"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chad Daniels (January 23 - January 24)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/114817</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/114817</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>With over a billion streams across his 8 albums, Chad Daniels is one of the most listened-to comedians of all time. A Minnesota native, Chad has spent over 20 years touring the country, bringing his sharp wit to audiences nationwide. He’s made 6 late-night appearances is one of only 13 comics ever featured on The Tonight Show with Conan O’Brien. Chad’s latest special, EMPTY NESTER, was shot in his hometown of Minnesota and recently premiered on Netflix. Chad co-hosts the podcast PRETEND PROBLEMS with his girlfriend Kelsey Cook, as well as Middle of Somewhere with his buddy Cy Amundson.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/69752/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Jay Oakerson (January 16 - January 18)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/108356</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/108356</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2026 11:15:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Big Jay Oakerson is one of the most beloved and easily recognizable comedians in New York City. His easy charm and dirty delivery endear him to audiences every night at The Comedy Cellar, The Stand and Stand Up New York. He’s no stranger to the rest of America, either, regularly headlining across the country and playing festivals including Bonaroo, Jager's Korn tour, Rock Star Energy Drink's Mayhem Fest, Gathering of the Juggalos and Funny or Die’s Oddball Festival. Jay has also recently been featured on This Is Not Happening with Ari Shaffir, Comedy Underground with Dave Attell, FX’s Louie, Inside Amy Schumer, and Late Night with Jimmy Fallon. This last year, Jay's Comedy Central hour special "Big Jay Oakerson: Live At Webster Hall" premiered. Filmed at the legendary music venue in New York City providing the perfect heavy metal vibe for the show. Jay's comedy is raw, compelling and honest to the core, as he takes viewers on a journey of brutal truths about his relationship with his teenage daughter, sexual tension between him and his best friend Dave and advise to women on how to delicately handle a man with an unfortunate penis size. His second album with Comedy Central Records, The Crowdwork Sessions: What’s Your F@#king Deal?! Recorded in 2013 live at The Stand, it captures Jay’s raunchy, off-the-cuff essence with a full hour of crowdwork. It joins Jay’s first album, An American Storyteller, a one-hour onslaught of unbridled awesomeness and raunchy rock n' roll hilarity recorded at Stand Up New York in 2009. Oakerson has hosted 2 seasons of "What's Your F@#king Deal?! Crowdwork &amp; Off The Cuff Comedy" on Seeso. Jay asks the audience to let go of pretension and leave egos at the door as he leads a pack of comics in a completely improvised show based on interactions with the crowd. The atmosphere is loose and no-holds-barred, so you'll see a side of the performers you've never seen before. He is co-host of two wildly popular podcasts - “The Most Offensive Podcast on Earth” Legion of Skanks with Luis J. Gomez and Dave Smith and The SDR (Sex, Drugs &amp; Rock &amp; Roll) Show with Ralph Sutton. He also the co-host's of The Bonfire on Comedy Central Radio Sirius XM 95 alongside Dan Soder evert Mondays through Thursday 6-8pm EST. Longtime fans of Jay’s will also remember him as Neil, the sexually ambiguous owner of a NYC rock club, on IFC’s Z-Rock, and from his appearances on Comedy Central's Premium Blend, Comedy Central Presents and Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn. He’s wowed audiences at the prestigious Just For Laughs Montreal festival an impressive four times, both on The Nasty Show and with his solo show, The American Storyteller. And he’s a fan favorite guest on Sirius XM’s Bennington (previously Ron &amp; Fez).</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/30990/full/data?1614481997"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodnights Presents: 50 First Jokes (January 13)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128592</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128592</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 8 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Hosted by Tyler Wood Description - Join 50 of North Carolina’s best comedians as they welcome in the new year with new material. This show features comedians telling their first new joke they’ve written since the year started. Here is a sign-up link for those who would like a chance to be on the show- https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfkbCESNYn0spcK4_C9sRwafyCp6-tYERwPspC-U7ZVW-TBFg/viewform?usp=dialog</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/59288/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Mic at Goodnights (January 14 - March 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128293</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128293</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 8 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>20+ comics, lots of laughs. Everyone starts somewhere. See the next big thing here! Make us your place for dinner, drinks and comedy!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/76972/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GiGi Leflair (February 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129034</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129034</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 7 Jan 2026 22:17:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Introducing Gigi LeFlair, the comedic sensation hailing from Woodruff, SC, whose infectious southern charm and razor-sharp wit have captivated audiences worldwide. With a staggering social media following of over 160,000 on Instagram, 270,000 on Facebook, and a whopping 500,000 on TikTok, Gigi is a true force to be reckoned with in the digital comedy sphere. Her hilarious videos, which boast an average of 60,000 views each, have solidified her status as a comedic powerhouse. Gigi's comedic prowess extends beyond the digital realm, as she has graced the stages of renowned comedy clubs such as The Comedy Zone, Stardome, Uptown Comedy Corner, and The Komedy Lounge, among others. Combining her southern charm with sharp observational humor, Gigi LeFlair continues to leave audiences roaring with laughter wherever she goes. Get ready to be entertained, delighted, and thoroughly amused.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/86440/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Silva (February 11)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128860</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128860</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 22:15:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Justin Silva was born and raised in New Haven, CT. He started doing comedy at the age of 21. Prior to comedy, he was an electrician full-time, and a server at chili’s part- time. The workforce was not working out for him. After his first comedy show, he learned it was where he belonged. Justin fell in love with being on the stage and making people laugh. A year and a half later, he quit his jobs to pursue his dream. Justin got on stage as much as he could. Attending open mics. Performing for free at comedy shows and accepting hosting gigs for very little to no money. In efforts to share his comedy with the world, he began making content and posting on social media. Buzz, traffic, and popularity all grew up and blew up. He decided, with his fiancé Ashley Cotto it was time to leave Connecticut and take the leap of faith to move to Florida. Justin continued to grind and work hard every day to become a bigger act. He wants to create people’s favorite space to laugh and is currently touring in a 2024 Worldwide Tour. He believes what you put in this game is what you get out of it. Justin will continue to put in all that he can, with great faith that he gets everything he can out of it. Creating content, performing comedy year-round while providing for his family, and keeping the faith in making a living; his 5 children are his main inspiration and drive him every day to conquer his dreams.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/79386/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Machi (April 11 - April 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128350</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128350</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 11:15:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Comedian Joe Machi was born and raised in State College, PA, the home of Penn State University. After college he held jobs at a supermarket and media company. Machi moved to New York in 2006 to pursue comedy. He has been seen performing stand up on Late Night with Jimmy Fallon, The CBC’s Just For Laughs Gala and has been a panelist on The Fox News program, Red Eye. Machi was also one of 10 comics selected to perform at the 2012 Montreal Just For Laughs New Faces showcase. His comedy has also been mentioned in The New York Times, NY Daily News, NY Post and Time Out New York. Other highlights include winning the 2010 NY Underground Comedy Festival’s Emerging Comic’s Contest, finishing second in the 2011 New York Comedy Contest, being a two time finalist in the New York Comedy Festivals Funniest Person Competition and being a finalist for the 2012 Andy Kaufman award. Machi has become a staple on New York Comedy Club and alt comedy shows as well as comedy festivals nation-wide.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/27856/full/data?1581364974"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Sabrina Wu (April 10 - April 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128349</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128349</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sabrina Wu is a New York based actor, writer, and stand-up comedian. They made their feature film debut in the Lionsgate comedy JOY RIDE, from executive producers Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg and director Adele Lim. They’ve also guest starred in ABBOTT ELEMENTARY, and you can soon watch them as a series regular in the upcoming show MURDERBOT starring Alexander Skarsgard on Apple TV+. Wu was a writer on the critically-acclaimed FX limited series DYING FOR SEX starring Michelle Williams and Jenny Slate. On the stand-up side, they were selected as one of the New Faces of Comedy by the Just For Laughs Festival in 2022. Later that fall, they had their TV debut doing stand up on the Tonight Show. Variety Magazine named Wu one of the Top 10 Comics to Watch in 2023. In the same year, Vulture Magazine named Wu a Comedian You Should Know and Will now.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85775/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Tallent (April 09)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128348</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128348</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sam Tallent (“the absurd voice of a surreal generation”- The Denver Post) is a comedian. For the last decade he has performed more than 40 weekends per year across America, Canada and Europe. His writing has appeared in Birdy Magazine and on VICE.com and he’s told jokes on Comedy Central, TruTV and VICELAND. His acclaimed debut novel, Running the Light, (Doug Stanhope: “the best fictional representation of comedy in any medium ever”, Marc Maron: “a beautiful rendering of a dark reality") has been heralded as the definitive book on stand up comedy. Waiting For Death to Claim Us, his comedy special, is available on Amazon Prime. He lives in Colorado with his wife and dog.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/38417/full/data?1642186527"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Eric D’Alessandro (March 20 - March 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128347</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128347</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 11:15:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Eric D’Alessandro is a charismatic New Yorker with an unfiltered sense of humor. His unique style, influenced by his Italian-American heritage, spins relatable narratives that resonate with everyday Americans. Starting with his early work on YouTube, Eric has developed a diverse portfolio which includes sketches, celebrity impressions, and comedic songs. His authentic characters, both live-action and animated, have garnered widespread acclaim. In particular, Eric's video "Where It Was" has amassed over 45 million views and has led to multiple film and television appearances. Eric frequently contributes to podcasts, including Barstool Sports' KFC Radio, Growing Up Italian, Jeff FM and The Dr. Drew Podcast. Eric routinely performs to sold-out stand-up crowds. Notable venues that have hosted Eric include The Borgata in Atlantic City, NJ; New Jersey’s Count Basie Theatre; NYCs Town Hall; the 1,900-seat St. George Theater in Staten Island, NY; and The Paramount in Huntington, NY. Eric's first comedy special, Eric D'Alessandro: I Don't Understand, is now streaming on Hulu.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/76630/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Holp (March 07)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128346</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128346</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jan 2026 11:15:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Travis Holp is an internationally recognized medium, author, and teacher who has helped thousands connect with loved ones in spirit. Certified by the Forever Family Foundation, Travis is known for delivering detailed, evidential messages with warmth, compassion, and a touch of humor.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/75114/full/data"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
