<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Goodnights Comedy Club Events</title>
    <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events</link>
    <description>Comedy events at Goodnights Comedy Club in Raleigh, NC</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:15:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Open Mic at Goodnights (January 21 - March 25)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128293</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128293</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:15:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>20+ comics, lots of laughs. Everyone starts somewhere. See the next big thing here! Make us your place for dinner, drinks and comedy!</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/76972/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Aidan McCluskey (May 01 - May 03)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129469</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/129469</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>At 19, Aidan McCluskey left his associate's degree to pursue comedy. Four months after his first open mic, he won Acme's Funniest Person Contest, becoming the youngest winner in contest history. After a stint in a Las Vegas based pyramid scheme, he returned to Minneapolis in 2021 and quickly became a regular at Acme Comedy Company. He now headlines regionally, and features for Shawn Gardini, Dan Soder, and tours with Nick Mullen. Aidan has appeared on the Adam Friedland Show and Barstool's The Yak, Son of a Boy Dad, and ANUS. He was also a performer at Skankfest in Las Vegas 2024 and hosts his semi-regular podcast, Goat Mentality.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/85474/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Silva (February 11)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128860</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128860</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Justin Silva was born and raised in New Haven, CT. He started doing comedy at the age of 21. Prior to comedy, he was an electrician full-time, and a server at chili’s part- time. The workforce was not working out for him. After his first comedy show, he learned it was where he belonged. Justin fell in love with being on the stage and making people laugh. A year and a half later, he quit his jobs to pursue his dream. Justin got on stage as much as he could. Attending open mics. Performing for free at comedy shows and accepting hosting gigs for very little to no money. In efforts to share his comedy with the world, he began making content and posting on social media. Buzz, traffic, and popularity all grew up and blew up. He decided, with his fiancé Ashley Cotto it was time to leave Connecticut and take the leap of faith to move to Florida. Justin continued to grind and work hard every day to become a bigger act. He wants to create people’s favorite space to laugh and is currently touring in a 2024 Worldwide Tour. He believes what you put in this game is what you get out of it. Justin will continue to put in all that he can, with great faith that he gets everything he can out of it. Creating content, performing comedy year-round while providing for his family, and keeping the faith in making a living; his 5 children are his main inspiration and drive him every day to conquer his dreams.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/79386/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Machi (April 11 - April 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128350</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128350</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Comedian Joe Machi was born and raised in State College, PA, the home of Penn State University. After college he held jobs at a supermarket and media company. Machi moved to New York in 2006 to pursue comedy. He has been seen performing stand up on Late Night with Jimmy Fallon, The CBC’s Just For Laughs Gala and has been a panelist on The Fox News program, Red Eye. Machi was also one of 10 comics selected to perform at the 2012 Montreal Just For Laughs New Faces showcase. His comedy has also been mentioned in The New York Times, NY Daily News, NY Post and Time Out New York. Other highlights include winning the 2010 NY Underground Comedy Festival’s Emerging Comic’s Contest, finishing second in the 2011 New York Comedy Contest, being a two time finalist in the New York Comedy Festivals Funniest Person Competition and being a finalist for the 2012 Andy Kaufman award. Machi has become a staple on New York Comedy Club and alt comedy shows as well as comedy festivals nation-wide.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/27856/full/data?1581364974"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Sabrina Wu (April 10 - April 12)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128349</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128349</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sabrina Wu is a New York based actor, writer, and stand-up comedian. They made their feature film debut in the Lionsgate comedy JOY RIDE, from executive producers Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg and director Adele Lim. They’ve also guest starred in ABBOTT ELEMENTARY, and you can soon watch them as a series regular in the upcoming show MURDERBOT starring Alexander Skarsgard on Apple TV+. Wu was a writer on the critically-acclaimed FX limited series DYING FOR SEX starring Michelle Williams and Jenny Slate. On the stand-up side, they were selected as one of the New Faces of Comedy by the Just For Laughs Festival in 2022. Later that fall, they had their TV debut doing stand up on the Tonight Show. Variety Magazine named Wu one of the Top 10 Comics to Watch in 2023. In the same year, Vulture Magazine named Wu a Comedian You Should Know and Will now.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/86433/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Tallent (February 13 - February 15)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128348</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128348</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sam Tallent (“the absurd voice of a surreal generation”- The Denver Post) is a comedian. For the last decade he has performed more than 40 weekends per year across America, Canada and Europe. His writing has appeared in Birdy Magazine and on VICE.com and he’s told jokes on Comedy Central, TruTV and VICELAND. His acclaimed debut novel, Running the Light, (Doug Stanhope: “the best fictional representation of comedy in any medium ever”, Marc Maron: “a beautiful rendering of a dark reality") has been heralded as the definitive book on stand up comedy. Waiting For Death to Claim Us, his comedy special, is available on Amazon Prime. He lives in Colorado with his wife and dog.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/seat-engine-files-production/talent/headshots/photos/38417/full/data?1642186527"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room 861 at Goodnights: Eric D’Alessandro (March 20 - March 22)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128347</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128347</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Eric D’Alessandro is a charismatic New Yorker with an unfiltered sense of humor. His unique style, influenced by his Italian-American heritage, spins relatable narratives that resonate with everyday Americans. Starting with his early work on YouTube, Eric has developed a diverse portfolio which includes sketches, celebrity impressions, and comedic songs. His authentic characters, both live-action and animated, have garnered widespread acclaim. In particular, Eric's video "Where It Was" has amassed over 45 million views and has led to multiple film and television appearances. Eric frequently contributes to podcasts, including Barstool Sports' KFC Radio, Growing Up Italian, Jeff FM and The Dr. Drew Podcast. Eric routinely performs to sold-out stand-up crowds. Notable venues that have hosted Eric include The Borgata in Atlantic City, NJ; New Jersey’s Count Basie Theatre; NYCs Town Hall; the 1,900-seat St. George Theater in Staten Island, NY; and The Paramount in Huntington, NY. Eric's first comedy special, Eric D'Alessandro: I Don't Understand, is now streaming on Hulu.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/86613/full/data"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Holp (March 07)</title>
      <link>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128346</link>
      <guid>https://www.goodnightscomedy.com/events/128346</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:15:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Travis Holp is an internationally recognized medium, author, and teacher who has helped thousands connect with loved ones in spirit. Certified by the Forever Family Foundation, Travis is known for delivering detailed, evidential messages with warmth, compassion, and a touch of humor.</description>
      <enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://files.seatengine.com/talent/headshots/photos/75114/full/data"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
